{
    "subject": "resource/Andy_Roberts_(musician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedMusicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Hank_Wangford",
    "human_readable": "Andy Roberts (musician) is associated with Hank Wangford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9821109175682068,
            "question": "Are there any other musicians associated with Andy Roberts and Hank Wangford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9817044734954834,
            "question": "In what genre of music are Andy Roberts and Hank Wangford associated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9718806743621826,
            "question": "Is there a musical connection between Andy Roberts and Hank Wangford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9593655467033386,
            "question": "How is the association between Andy Roberts and Hank Wangford significant in the music world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9072479605674744,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of musical styles shared by Andy Roberts and Hank Wangford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7840612530708313,
            "question": "Have Andy Roberts and Hank Wangford collaborated on any projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7715835571289062,
            "question": "Who is Andy Roberts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7096937298774719,
            "question": "What is Hank Wangford known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6776602268218994,
            "question": "What are some notable works by Hank Wangford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5861015915870667,
            "question": "What are some notable works by Andy Roberts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andy Roberts (musician) is associated with Hank Wangford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4231_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable works by Hank Wangford?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4231_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Hank Wangford known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4231_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Andy Roberts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4231_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4231_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Brad Breath (alias Andy Roberts) has played with Hank Wangford and many others, including The Scaffold, Bonzo Dog, Plainsong, Billy Connolly, Pink Floyd, and many others. This suggests a strong association between Andy Roberts (musician) and Hank Wangford."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that both Andrew \"Andy\" Roberts and Hank Wangford have collaborated or performed together, supporting the association between them."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}